Marco analysis

Pre-study questions (perhaps instead of just streams, include videos as well)
- streams - not that often (maybe once or twice a week)
- managing time — pretty well, not stay too long
- never interact with the chat in streams
- toxicity - randomly, and often

The thing
- “if you want to stop at any time, please feel free to do so”

- task 1 - click a video
	done :)

- task 2
	tried to click the tabs (not interactive)
	tabs not really working, go back to the other tab (view tabs is working for him :) )

- task 3
	tried clicking menu
	remembers time control thing, can go back!! — did not use the arrow button

	specify what the duration is, not very clear (or maybe larger info button)

- task 4
	clicked twice on home to get back to home ?!? From the second set screen

- trolls and windows
	trying to click the eye to make it not visible, and using the menu button
		instead of the settings gear … maybe change that symbol?

- isolated group chat
	make create group text larger (oops)
	:)) good

Make the arrow more obvious
	make the interaction for the tabs there

Post-study questionnaire
Q1 - 2 - not many trouble, and not really mind the comments (doesn’t watch very much anyways)
Q2 -  2 - some of the things not implemented but easy to use
Q3 - agree - not very complex, very obvious
Q4 - strongly disagree - just need to play around with it :)
Q5 - agree - the chat was nice and seamless to open the menu 
Q6 - disagree - not many inconsistencies
Q7 - strongly agree - easy to figure out
Q8 - disagree - pretty easy to use
Q9 - agree - I guess meh
Q10 - disagree

Recommend to friends/family - 5/6 (pretty niche problem and few ppl he knows has this issues)

In the form, ask for the ta
- Intro - avoid giving benefits or problems about it, want the unbiased opinion of the participant (want the positive and negative feedback when they go through)
- Some of the terms are subjective to some people (like definition to toxicity or steaming)
- Describe their previous experiences with streams or watching streams (see if it comes out naturally for the time management aspect)
- prove to see what they were thinking instead of just watching (what they are clicking and what they are expecting)
- tasks themselves, instead of specific alarms, leave these kind of things more general, where we avoid x amount of time doing something to find and understand a related functionality