idea: tutorial so people familiar with the new tabs and stuff

3rd note-taker job

Pre-study
- live streaming content, not too much — more of a Netflix person
- managing time watching things — end up watching for too long probably or falling asleep
- not too much interactions (need to for giving feedback, she will participate and type in responses)
- hate comments — can be rephrased I think, negative comments or negativity is better

The thing
- task 1 - click a video
	very clean, all the videos have thumbnails, so easy to scan
		scroll bar not working (cannot scroll)

- task 2 - lengthy, find a new video
	looking at the navigation on the left to see if there’s recommendations
		recommendations bar is a good idea :o
	seeing a repeat of that menu on the live chat system
	clicking the side-bar (very confusing)
		new tab is an issue right now!!!!
	
- task 3 - time control
	tried to add an event instead of using the one time alarm — maybe repeated events is not clear
	next thoughts is the alarm
		all works :)))

- task 4 - go back to that video, use chat
	history button should be working
	click on reactions, or get a menu of things :)
	
- task 5 - negative comments (long messages)
	click the eye icon to hide that person
	did not see the settings gear — maybe make it different from the other settings gear
		confusion about the settings gear (turn off individuals)

- task 6 - personal group
	good, clicked create group

Feedback
	enough things she could click on to get a feel of how the system would work if it was built out
	liked our concern for negative people/comments (promotes positivity)
	little things about interactivity — expected a back button (navigation is limited so can still figure it out)
	felt comfortable testing and clicking around things
	the facilitator at the beginning a little tired :(
	she did not feel any judgement for doing something wrong or not intended, so very positive

Hey did you notice this, can you try this out (taken notes that they didn’t discover it)