Notes
Pre-study questions
How often do you watch live streaming content — 5-6 times a week
How well are u able to manage time when watching live streams — non heavy course load, he can watch more
How often do you use the chat in live streams — not too often, because the streamer he watches has a ton of viewers so the chat is often folded, so no need to type like that
How many negative comments when reading the comment — not often, very rare he sees something negative.

Begin - Prototype and screen share
Task 1 - scroll through the trending page, select the one with the right title

Task 2 - make a different tab, watch smash bros in the meantime just click into it

Task 3 - How to set a reminder for 90 minutes from now
Get a timer, not sure if the time control is the right button
Went Home, goes off in an hour and 30, when alarm goes off he goes off and does work

Task 4 - use the chat (express feelings)
Usually, have friends in a voice chat and express what they’re thinking — elsewhere
Or use the chat or clip the scene and share with friends

Click the chat channel, type into there

Task 5 - toxic chat, remove those unwanted comments
There isn’t a way to remove individual comments, usually just close the chat and go elsewhere to not view it

Task 6 - want to talk with a specific play with someone else, the rest of chat talks about something else - how to find ppl to talk about this play with
Maybe the team he’s cheering for has a discord channel
Or maybe someone with similar chat goals/comments, can dm them

If no discord, scroll through the chat to see other peoples opinions

Create Group or maybe a group that already exists (maybe find a group)
— yea done, it works :)
Yep it works, tried to add friends into the chat, interacting with the buttons

Back to task 4 (negative comments)
- what would help remove automatically unwanted comments
Randomly clicked on moderator settings, so remove all those things (and blacklist people)
- want to fix the moderator settings button

Post scenario questions
What do you like?
	struggling figuring out what to do (something that doesn’t exist currently), so it is a nice addition to the current systems

What do you dislike?
	The find a group, if there are actual trolls, they’d probably join the group and mass flood that group chat (moderator settings within group chats)

How easy was it to use?
	It took some getting used to, like figuring out the moderator settings
	After knowing about the buttons, it was  rather easy to use

Do you think this is something you need actual text/something to navigate through this (or just playing around with this to figure things out)
	A very fast tutorial or something to help quickly understand

Any other changes you think is a good idea?
	the time management one is pretty cool to have a time managing app to help control that

Scale of 0-10 recommend to other people?
	He would, probably give a 7 on the scale