Manages time pretty well,
Watches streams a few times a week
Interacts with the chat consistently
More than he can count

Prototype testing
First task its pretty simple, he found it

Task 2: copy and paste into a new tab, and click on a different live stream
He would use the chrome tab extension instead of our tab system

Task 3: time management - set a reminder to start working from now
Usually, just uses the time on his computer to see how much time there is left
If he was worried, set an actual computer timer for himself

Clicks on time control
Creates a new event instead of an alarm (daily or weekly) to help with the work that he needs done

Task 4: click back or view tabs
- go back by clicking the tabs :)
 —> reacting to the streams
- (Maybe add a chat button) probably click reactions or cheers

Task 5: embarrassingly bad play
how to auto remove comments?
- maybe make a new group or use cheers for positivity
-  moderation settings, filter the chat :)
How to manually remove unwanted comments in the chat
- maybe click on each persons profiles, or filter out specific words

Task 6: creating a group, specifically for a given play
- he could create a group of like-minded people
- find a group or create a group?
	- found the button pretty quickly

Post-study questions
What do you like about the system
	Really likes the tab system — most streaming sites, can only have 2 at once on other main streaming sites
	greater user functionality to switch between tabs on streams without messing your own stream up

What do you not like about the system,
	The timer system is a little harder to use - not really searching for how to control your own time
	The little box/timetable, designer dissonance between what to watch on twitch and time controls imposed on yourself

How to improve,
	Just one big box instead of many different things (remove repeating events)
	It feels very formal and scheduled, unlike streaming sites
	Something intuitive and streamlined

Any other feedback?
	Nope, everything seems pretty good

Chat:
	Pretty alright however, like the timing system, its a little harder to use (maybe because he doesn’t use specialized chat function son stream sites)
		not used the that functionality maybe
		Twitch chat

Overall, was it hard to use, easy to use?
	At first glance, harder to use since he is unfamiliar with the UI
	If the came back more and more, he’d probably enjoy it

Scale of 0 to 10, how likely to recommend to others
	a 4 or 5, most of his friends are used to twitch or YouTube livestreams
		unless they really want a customized platform/technical, cater to themselves, then he would recommend this to others

Grey is kind of a boring colour

Want to add functionality, more tabs?

Maybe include “using our system” for our tasks