Pre-study
- How often do you watch live-streaming content : once or twice a week
- How well do you manage time when watching : Pretty well, typically during exam season, he is not watching anything (during the ofttimes, typically manages it pretty well)
		Reserves one day for himself
- How often do you interact with chat : not often
		Reason : its not really his method of engagement (just there to watch the streamer as a source of entertainment)
- Negative comments when reading chat : the types of streams he watches, very few negative comments

Usability Test
- Finding the livestream for the finals this year
		Just go into the search bar to find what he needs specifically : not typically watch trending videos
		Just clicking it

- Interact with new tabs/returning to this video
		Tried clicking the buttons but they do not seem to be working ( feel free to play around )

- Deadline coming up, need to manage time
		Trying to find a settings button
		If not, then just watch the 90 minutes he wants to watch, then he just makes a decision afterwards
		Trying to click buttons, groups and things, and settings — option to set a timer — Finding a group to help set the timer for him, or keep each other on time

- Awkward, need to be more flexible with tasks

- Filter system
		Moderation settings (clicking through it)
		Blocking players and filtering messages

- Manually getting rid of comments
		Tried to black list the players (clicking the eye icon works for him!)

- creating a group
		yep done :D
		Invite friends

Post-study questions
		Liked - Viewer to control and moderate their own chat/texts is good to filter out things
		Disliked - Have that menu specifically int eh stream menu as well (hard to find the timer buttons)
		Complexity - pretty clear cut and straight forward after playing around with it a bit
		Final Thoughts - commendations, anything to change — nope, thinks its pretty clean
		Likelihood to recommend to someone else — Probably around an 8
